http://www.folkharp.com/content/2-legal-notice

Cart
0
Product
Products
(empty)
Avesian, Holly
Bach, K.P.E.
Dunwoodie, Anna
Dussek, J. L.
Freed, Norris
Friml, R./Elster, R.
Goodwin, Roxana
Gounod/Landy, M.
Gustavson, Nancy
Guy, Stanley E.
Holsinger, Kevin
Holst/Witman, J.
Keyes, Julie
Kleinstuber, Cindy (Blevins)
Mayberry, Matt
Mayer, D. / Tucker, M.
Persichetti, Vincent
Pescetti, G.B.
American Historical & Patriotic
Audition & Recital Repertoire (Pedal)
Christmas & Winter
Classical (1751 - 1820)
Early Music (600 - 1750)
Recent Compositions
Romantic & Post (1820 - present)
Therapeutic
Seasonal (non-Xmas)
Christmas & Winter
Classical (1751 - 1820)
Folk, Ethnic & Celtic
Early Music (600 - 1750)
Recent Compositions
Romantic & Post (1820 - present)
Seasonal (not Xmas)
Worship & Wedding
Latin American
Harp & Flute
Christmas & Winter
Classical (1751 - 1820)
Early Music (600 - 1750)
Folk, Ethnic & Celtic
Judaica
Original Works or Material
Pop, Jazz, & Film
Romantic & Post (1820 - present)
Christmas & Winter
Classical (1751 - 1820)
Early Music (600 - 1750)
Folk, Ethnic & Celtic
Judaica
Original Works
Pop, Jazz, & Film
Romantic & Post (1820-present)
Recent Compositions
Seasonal (not Xmas)
Harp & Voice
Classical (1751 - 1820)
Christmas & Winter
Early Music (600 - 1750)
Recent Compositions
Romantic & Post (1820 - present)
Worship and Wedding
Festive (non-Christmas)
Grix, Christa
Guy, Stanley E.
Concert Grand
Semi Grand (46 Strings)
Lyon & Healy
What's New!
Legal
User Agreement:    We strive to bring you accurate and up-to-date material, though we make no guarantees that everything on this site is completely accurate, as our vendors (people and companies from which we purchase inventory) often change and update their materials and their prices. We may slip up and occasionally forget to change a product design/style/price in a timely manner, although we try to keep up with all the changes. On occasion a product is discontinued; there may be a slight delay in removing it from our site.     Melody’s Traditional Music/Afghan Press assumes no liability or responsibility for any damage to you, your computer, or other property, due to your access to, use of, or downloading from this site or any materials/information provided on this site. Our web site is stored at Go Daddy, and free from viruses. We are happy to provide links to teachers and performers who may help you along your musical path, however; these hyperlinks are maintained/controlled by others. Since we provide this as a service, we do not necessarily endorse the contents of these websites, nor do we routinely review these sites.     Many of the images, trademarks or servicemarks appearing on the Site are the marks of their respective owners and manufacturers. We have been given permission to use them. If you have any questions about this User Agreement, contact Melody’s Traditional Music. If you do not agree with the terms of this User Agreement, you may not use this website.     We reserve the right to change this User Agreement at any time without notice.     Privacy Notice: We do not share our customer list with other stores. (We don't have time for this nonsense).Your credit card numbers are not stored in our on-site computers, so if you call with your order, please have your credit card handy. These are recorded by hand, hard copy is immediately shredded.     We have made the decision to discontinue our paper catalog. Please hang onto your 2009 catalog. We will be placing updates of new products onto our web site. E-mail announcements are sent when new publications come out, and for relevant events. We use Constant Contact, a safe and reputable company, for our e-mailing list. We have several social media outlets:     http://melodystraditionalmusic.wordpress.com/    http://publishingharpmusic.wordpress.com/    Our FB page: https://www.facebook.com/HarpMelody     Descriptions of Music:We began writing detailed descriptions of the music we carry back in 1994, when we published our first catalog. We spend much time looking through the music and coming up with the details we think will help you decide if it is for you or not. Our descriptions are honest, thoughtful and sometimes humorous. Our descriptions are copyrighted © 1994 - 2012. Please ask permission to use them.
This Web site was created using PrestaShop™ open-source software.
Privacy Statement relavent to GDPR
Melody's Traditional Music and Afghan Press Music for the Harp are under the umbrella company Melody Productions, a Texas S Corporation. Both companies sell printed harp music, both paper and digital downloads. Melody's physical store also sells harps, both new and used. Melody Productions owns the following web sites: www.folkharp.com, www.afghanpress.com, www.afghanpressmusic.com, and melodystraditionalmusic.com. The latter site is a blog site. Www.folkharp.com sells paper music, some accessories for harp, and digital downloads. Both Afghan Press sites strictly sell paper music, and mostly to wholesale accounts. By using any of the Services above, you hereby agree to the collection and use of information as defined in this Privacy Policy.
This is intended as a global Privacy Policy, for all customers/individuals using our Services, noting certain rights and principles are applicable to, and reserved for, EU citizens and the handling of their personal data (i.e. the areas that refer to the  General Data Protection Regulation or ‘GDPR’).
Responsibilities:
We consider the input of data into our software as being sufficient evidence of Informed Consent being freely given by customers for the purchase of harp print music, both paper and digital. Your information is:
Processed Lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner;
Collected for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes;
Adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary;
Accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date;
Retained only for as long as necessary; and,
Processed securely in an appropriate manner to maintain security.
If you are an EU citizen whose personal information we hold, the GDPR affords certain rights. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please email melodytradmusic@gmail.com to process your request securely, we reserve the right to request you to provide two valid forms of identification for verification purposes.
Your rights are as follows:
The right to be informed;
The right of access;
The right to rectification;
The right to erasure (the ‘right to be forgotten’);
The right to restrict processing;
The right to data portability;
The right to object; and,
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling.
In our role as a commercial music store, we strive to uphold these rights in the manner, and to the timelines, defined within GDPR. Customers must also uphold these rights for these individuals. If we consider requests to: be frivolous; necessitate disproportionate effort to complete; or, cannot be fulfilled for another legitime reason (e.g. legal) – then we reserve the right to refuse them. If such an exceptional circumstance arises, then we will inform you (within a reasonable timeframe). If answering requests is likely to require additional time (above that specified in GDPR) or generates a commercially unreasonable expense (which you may have to meet, in part or in full), then we will also inform you (within a reasonable timeframe).
Timelines:
On matters where GDPR specifies a defined timeline, then we will strive to address them ‘within a reasonable timeline’ as recommended within GDPR.
Information
We collect several different types of information from Customers including:
Registration and Contact Information. We collect information about you when you (a) register to use the Services; and/or, (b) provide contact information to us via email, telephone, or through our Services.
Payment Information. When you purchase products via PayPal, we collect transactional information, which does not include your credit card information, but does include your billing and mailing address and anything else necessary to complete purchase.
When you purchase products through phone call, we collect transactional information, which may include your credit card information, billing and mailing address and anything else necessary to complete purchase.
Third Parties. We do not interact with advertisements and/or other content on external sites or platforms. We have Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest. We do not collect information from those sites.
Other Information. We are not aware of any other ways we collect information from you.
Transfer:
Melody Productions is a Texas S Corporation. Our website is hosted by Techlab in West Allis, WI. Our files are not stored in the cloud. We also consider the input of data into our software as being sufficient evidence of Informed Consent for said transfer of your own data.
Security:
We take the security of all data extremely seriously and utilize multiple technologies, processes and protocols to protect against the loss or theft of personal data, including (but not limited to): encryption, access controls, data backups, passwords, and reputable third parties (e.g. Paypal) et al.  This being said, although we invest at a commercially reasonable level, no software platform or data storage can be 100% secure; thus, we cannot make guarantees relating to data security. We do not sell, distribute or lease any personal information outside of our business, without obtaining Informed Consent, unless we are legally required to do so, or there is a ‘good faith belief’ such action is absolutely necessary.  For example, if Melody Productions sells or merges, then personal data will be transferred; in this case, we will provide advance notice. Disclosure could also be required to: protect the rights or assets of our business; prevent or investigate a wrongdoing related to our Services; support a legal request from a recognized legal authority; and/or, protect the safety of users of the Services et al.
Providers:
We use third-parties (including, but not limited to those listed, beneath) to monitor, analyze, support, promote and enhance our Services. In some cases, these providers will use personal data to fulfil their contractual obligations (with us), when we request them to perform various services on a legitimate interest basis:
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic and usage:http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
Google Adwords remarketing service is a personalized advertising service offered by Google Inc.: http://www.google.com/settings/ads (have not used this account since 2014)
PayPal processes payments: https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Constant Contact  is used for email marketing.
PrestaShop, a French company, is the tool/platform used to design our website.
Www.techlab.com monitors our site 24/7 and fixes all bugs
Use of Services, Website Visits and Support    Data relating to your online activity on our websites with respect to our Services, including the following:            IP address            browser type and version            geographic location            pages you view            how you got to our Services and any links you click on to leave our Services            when you update your information, communicate with us, or order new Services            metadata about your use and your contacts’ use of our Services and your emails you send (including clicks and opens)            your interactions with any videos we offer            issues you encounter requiring our support or assistance            any device or other method of communication you use to interact with the ServicesThis data is collected in a variety of places including system log files and back end databases.
Contact:
For legal and formal purposes, our registered office is 21626 Gentry Rd, Cypress, TX 77429, USA. 281-890-4500
Copyright © 2014 Melody's Traditional Music & Harp Shoppe. All rights reserved.
